Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
  - Area J - Wessex, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    - Hampshire, Eastleigh, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/471; 1.0 file
    - Hampshire, New Forest, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/472; 1.0 file
    - Hampshire, Petersfield, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/473; 1.0 file
    - Hampshire, Winchester, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/474; 1.0 file
    - Isle of Wight, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/475; 1.0 file
    - Oxford, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/476; 1.0 file
    - Oxfordshire, Banbury, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/477; 1.0 file
    - Oxfordshire, Henley, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/478; 1.0 file
    - Swindon, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/479; 1.0 file
    - Wiltshire, Chippenham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/480; 1.0 file
    - Wiltshire, Devizes, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/481; 1.0 file
    - Wiltshire, Salisbury, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/482; 1.0 file
    - Wiltshire, Westbury, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/483; 1.0 file
  - Area K - Western, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    CCO 1/14/484-CCO 1/14/511
    - Bristol, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/484/489; 1.0 file
    - Bristol Central, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/484; 1.0 file
    - Bristol North East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/485; 1.0 file
    - Bristol North West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/486; 1.0 file
    - Bristol South, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/487; 1.0 file
    - Bristol South East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/488; 1.0 file
    - Bristol West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/489; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, Bodmin, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/490; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, Falmouth and Camborne, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/491; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/492; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, St. Ives, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/493; 1.0 file
    - Cornwall, Truro, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/494; 1.0 file
    - Exeter, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/495; 1.0 file
    - Plymouth, Devonport, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/496; 1.0 file
    - Plymouth, Sutton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/497; 1.0 file
    - Torquay, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/498; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Honiton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/499; 1.0 file
    - Devon North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/500; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Tavistock, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/501; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Tiverton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/502; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Torrington, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/503; 1.0 file
    - Devon, Totnes, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/504; 1.0 file
    - Bath, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/505; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Bridgwater, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/506; 1.0 file
    - Somerset North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/507; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Taunton, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/508; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Wells, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/509; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Weston-super-Mare, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/510; 1.0 file
    - Somerset, Yeovil, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/511; 1.0 file
  - Area L - Wales and Monmouthshire, Dec 1961-Jan 1968
    CCO 1/14/512-CCO 1/14/547
    The remainder of the series after CCO 1/14/547 is missing.
    - Anglesey, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/512; 1.0 file
    - Brecon and Radnor, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/513; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Caernarvon, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/514; 1.0 file
    - Caernarvon, Conway, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/515; 1.0 file
    - Cardigan, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/516; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/517/1; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/517/2; 1.0 file
    - Carmarthen, Llanelly, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/518; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/519; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/520; 1.0 file
    - Flint East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/521; 1.0 file
    - Flint West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/522; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/523; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/524/526; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff North, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/524; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff South East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/525; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/526; 1.0 file
    - Merthyr Tydfil, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/527; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/528; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/529; 1.0 file
    - Swansea East, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/530; 1.0 file
    - Swansea West, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/531; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Aberavon, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/532; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Barry, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/533; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Caerphilly, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/534; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Gower, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/535; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Neath, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/536; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Ogmore, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/537; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Pontypridd, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/538/1; 1.0 file
    - South Wales Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/538/2; 1.0 file
    - South East Wales Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/538/3; 1.0 file
    - South West Wales Group, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/538/4; 1.0 file
    - Merioneth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/539; 1.0 file
    - Newport, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/540; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/541/1; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/541/2; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Bedwellty, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/542; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Ebbw Vale, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/543; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Monmouth, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/544; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/545; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/546; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, By-Election, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/546; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, By-Election - G.D.'s file, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/546; 1.0 file
    - Pembroke, Dec 1961-Jan 1968; CCO 1/14/547; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Feb 1968-Sep 1971
  CCO 1/15/104/2
  - University of London Graduates Association, Feb 1968-Sep 1971; CCO 1/15/104/2; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, 1971-1982
  - Area A - Greater London, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/1/1-CCO 1/16/1/6
    - Lambeth Central, Apr 1973-Apr 1978; CCO 1/16/1/1; 1.0 file
    - St Marylebone, Mar 1973-Mar 1975; CCO 1/16/1/2; 1.0 file
    - Paddington, Dec 1973-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/1/3; 1.0 file
    - Edmonton, Apr 1972-Jun 1975; CCO 1/16/1/4; 1.0 file
    - Islington Central, Aug 1972-Sep 1979; CCO 1/16/1/5; 1.0 file
    - Hackney Central, Jan 1973-Jan 1979; CCO 1/16/1/6; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/2/1-CCO 1/16/2/19
    - Wallsend, Feb 1973-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/2/1; 1.0 file
    - Blaydon, Nov 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/2/2; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Mar 1973-Jan 1974; Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/2/3; 1.0 file
    - Hexham, May-1973-Feb 1978; CCO 1/16/2/4; 1.0 file
    - Morpeth, Apr 1972-Feb 1979; CCO 1/16/2/5; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, May 1971-Jun 1979; CCO 1/16/2/6; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South [Includes some material relating to Sunderland North], Jul 1972-May 1977; CCO 1/16/2/7; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Feb 1972-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/2/8; 1.0 file
      [Includes copies of The New Wearside Observer, quarterly magazine of the Sunderland Conservative Association, Dec 1976 and Summer 1978].
    - South Shields, Mar 1973-May 1979; CCO 1/16/2/9; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle upon Tyne West, Mar 1972-Jun 1979; CCO 1/16/2/10; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle upon Tyne North, May 1974-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/2/11; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle upon Tyne East, Jan 1973-May 1978; CCO 1/16/2/12; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle upon Tyne Central, Sep 1972-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/2/13; 1.0 file
    - Jarrow, Feb 1972-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/2/14; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, May 1974-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/2/15; 1.0 file
    - Houghton-le-Spring, Oct 1972-Jun 1979; CCO 1/16/2/16; 1.0 file
    - Hartlepool, May 1971-Dec 1978; CCO 1/16/2/16; 1.0 file
    - Teeside Middlesbrough, Sep 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/2/17; 1.0 file
    - Teeside Redcar, Jul 1972-Dec 1978; CCO 1/16/2/18
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Aug 1972-Nov 1978; CCO 1/16/2/19; 1.0 file
      [Between 1974-1982 the constituency was known as Teesside Stockton]
  - Area C - North West, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/3/1-CCO 1/16/3/9
    - Manchester Withington, Jul 1973-Feb 1974; Feb 1980; CCO 1/16/3/1; 1.0 file
    - Nantwich, Sep 1972-Dec 1973; Apr-Aug 1976; CCO 1/16/3/2; 1.0 file
    - Altrincham and Sale, Sep 1972-Jun 1975; CCO 1/16/3/3; 1.0 file
    - Wirral, Apr 1974-Mar 1976; 1978; CCO 1/16/3/4; 1.0 file
    - Knutsford, Feb-Oct 1973; CCO 1/16/3/5; 1.0 file
    - Morecambe and Lonsdale, Nov 1977-1978; CCO 1/16/3/6; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Jul 1971-Nov 1973; Feb 1980; CCO 1/16/3/7; 1.0 file
    - City of Chester, Mar 1972-May 1973; Dec 1975; CCO 1/16/3/8; 1.0 file
    - Chorley, May 1972-Jun 1976; 1979; CCO 1/16/3/9; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/4/1-CCO 1/16/4/14
    - Barnsley, May 1972-May 1976; CCO 1/16/4/1; 1.0 file
    - Batley & Morley, Dec 1971-May 1976; CCO 1/16/4/2; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Oct 1972-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/4/3; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse & Spenborough, Jun 1973-Feb 1976; CCO 1/16/4/4; 1.0 file
    - Bradford West, Oct 1972-Aug 1976; CCO 1/16/4/5; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Aug 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/4/6; 1.0 file
    - Ripon, Oct 1972-Oct 1973; CCO 1/16/4/7; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Feb 1972-Nov 1973; Jul 1979; CCO 1/16/4/8; 1.0 file
    - Thirsk and Malton, Feb-Nov 1972; CCO 1/16/4/9; 1.0 file
    - Cleveland and Whitby, Feb 1972-Nov 1973; Feb 1978; CCO 1/16/4/10; 1.0 file
    - Harrogate, Apr 1972; Oct 1973-Jul 1974; CCO 1/16/4/11; 1.0 file
    - Bridlington, Dec 1976-May 1977; CCO 1/16/4/12; 1.0 file
    - Skipton, Apr 1974-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/4/13; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Feb 1972-Feb 1979; CCO 1/16/4/14; 1.0 file
  - Area E - East Midlands, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/5
    - Grantham, Dec 1974-Oct 1977; CCO 1/16/5/1; 1.0 file
    - Daventry, Mar 1973; Apr 1975; Nov 1978; CCO 1/16/5/2; 1.0 file
    - Blaby, Jul 1971-Nov 1973; CCO 1/16/5/3; 1.0 file
    - Northampton North, Feb 1972-Sep 1975; CCO 1/16/5/4; 1.0 file
    - Northampton South, Feb 1972-Aug 1973; CCO 1/16/5/5; 1.0 file
    - Melton, May 1973-Jan 1974; CCO 1/16/5/6; 1.0 file
  - Area F - West Midlands, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/6/1-CCO 1/16/6/23
    - Stoke-on-Trent North, Jul 1973-Dec 1982; CCO 1/16/6/1; 1.0 file
    - Stoke-on-Trent Central, Jan 1974-Nov 1982; CCO 1/16/6/2; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle-under-Lyne, Jan 1971-Dec 1982; CCO 1/16/6/3; 1.0 file
    - The Wrekin, Mar 1973-Jan 1983; CCO 1/16/6/4; 1.0 file
    - Shrewsbury, Jan 1972-Sep 1982; CCO 1/16/6/5; 1.0 file
    - Oswestry, May 1973-Jun 1974; CCO 1/16/6/6; 1.0 file
    - Ludlow, Sep 1969; Sep 1972-Aug 1976; CCO 1/16/6/7; 1.0 file
    - South Worcestershire, Sep 1971-Sep 1977; CCO 1/16/6/8; 1.0 file
    - Leominster, Aug 1972-Mar 1973; CCO 1/16/6/9; 1.0 file
    - Kidderminster, Nov 1972-Mar 1981; CCO 1/16/6/10; 1.0 file
    - Hereford, Jun 1972-Jun 1976; CCO 1/16/6/11; 1.0 file
    - Bromsgrove & Redditch, Apr-May 1975; CCO 1/16/6/12; 1.0 file
    - Worcester, Mar 1973; CCO 1/16/6/13; 1.0 file
    - West Gloucestershire, Mar 1974-Oct 1979; CCO 1/16/6/14; 1.0 file
    - Stroud, Apr 1974; CCO 1/16/6/15; 1.0 file
    - Gloucester, Jun 1972-Mar 1974; CCO 1/16/6/16; 1.0 file
    - Cheltenham, Jan-Jul 1974; CCO 1/16/6/17; 1.0 file
    - Meriden, Oct 1972-Sep 1975; May 1982; CCO 1/16/6/18; 1.0 file
    - Lichfield and Tamworth, Jul 1972-Jul 1980; CCO 1/16/6/19; 1.0 file
    - Sutton Coldfield, Mar 1972-Mar 1973; CCO 1/16/6/20; 1.0 file
    - Dudley West, Nov 1971-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/6/21; 1.0 file
    - South West Staffordshire, Nov 1971-Jan 1973; Feb 1980-Oct 1981; CCO 1/16/6/22; 1.0 file
    - Coventry South West, Nov 1971-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/6/23; 1.0 file
  - Area G - Eastern, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/7/1-CCO 1/16/7/16
    - Eye, Oct 1972-Aug 1975; Dec 1978; CCO 1/16/7/1; 1.0 file
    - St Albans, Nov 1972-Feb 1975; CCO 1/16/7/2; 1.0 file
    - Maldon, Dec 1968-Jan 1974; CCO 1/16/7/3; 1.0 file
    - Basildon, Mar 1972-Feb 1975; CCO 1/16/7/4; 1.0 file
    - Thurrock, Mar 1974-Feb 1977; CCO 1/16/7/5; 1.0 file
    - South West Hertfordshire, Nov 1972-Apr 1973; Nov 1979; CCO 1/16/7/6
    - Hemel Hempstead, Apr 1972-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/7/7; 1.0 file
    - South Norfolk, Aug 1969; Apr 1973-Aug 1974; CCO 1/16/7/8; 1.0 file
    - Cambridge, Dec 1972-Dec 1976; CCO 1/16/7/9; 1.0 file
    - Saffron Walden, Apr 1972-Apr 1973; Jun 1977; CCO 1/16/7/10; 1.0 file
    - Braintree, Feb 1972-Dec 1973; CCO 1/16/7/11; 1.0 file
    - Huntingdonshire, Apr-Jun 1973; CCO 1/16/7/12; 1.0 file
    - Hertford and Stevenage, Aug 1973-Feb 1976; CCO 1/16/7/13; 1.0 file
    - Welwyn and Hatfield, Jan 1974-May 1975; CCO 1/16/7/14; 1.0 file
    - Luton East, Mar 1974-Feb 1976; CCO 1/16/7/15; 1.0 file
    - Luton West, Jul 1972-Oct 1975; CCO 1/16/7/16; 1.0 file
  - Area H - Home Counties South East, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/8
    - Hastings and St Leonards, Nov 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/1; 1.0 file
    - Brighton Pavilion, Mar 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/2; 1.0 file
    - Chichester, Dec 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/3; 1.0 file
    - East Grinstead, Sep 1972-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Worthing, Mar 1973-Spring 1978; CCO 1/16/8/5; 1.0 file
    - Horsham and Crawley, Feb 1973-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/8/6; 1.0 file
    - Hove and Portslade, Dec 1973-Dec 1977; CCO 1/16/8/7; 1.0 file
    - Arundel, Mar 1971-Dec 1977; CCO 1/16/8/8; 1.0 file
    - Rye and Bexhill, Sep 1972-Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/8/9; 1.0 file
    - Mid-Sussex, Aug 1971-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/8/10; 1.0 file
    - Lewes, Mar 1973-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/11; 1.0 file
    - Eastbourne, Aug 1971-Apr 1978; CCO 1/16/8/12; 1.0 file
    - Shoreham, Dec 1972-Jan 1978; CCO 1/16/8/13; 1.0 file
    - Sevenoaks, Oct 1971-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/8/14; 1.0 file
    - Royal Tunbridge Wells, Dec 1973-Dec 1976; CCO 1/16/8/15; 1.0 file
    - Ashford, Sep 1973-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/8/16; 1.0 file
    - Folkestone and Hythe, Sep 1972-Jun 1982; CCO 1/16/8/17; 1.0 file
    - Dartford, Feb 1973-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/8/18; 1.0 file
    - Rochester and Chatham, Jan 1972-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/8/19; 1.0 file
  - Area J - Wessex, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/9/1-CCO 1/16/9/19
    - Chippenham, Jan-Mar 1973; Apr-Aug 1976; CCO 1/16/9/1
    - Henley, May-Sep 1972; CCO 1/16/9/2; 1.0 file
    - Petersfield [East Hampshire], Mar 1971-Nov 1974; CCO 1/16/9/3; 1.0 file
    - Newbury, Jun 1973-Mar 1975; CCO 1/16/9/4; 1.0 file
    - Eton and Slough, Jun 1972-Dec 1975; CCO 1/16/9/5; 1.0 file
    - Mid-Oxon, Mar 1973-Jan 1974; CCO 1/16/9/6; 1.0 file
    - Winchester, Jan 1972-Jul 1977; CCO 1/16/9/7; 1.0 file
    - Reading North, Jan 1972-Jan 1973; CCO 1/16/9/8; 1.0 file
    - Abingdon, May 1973; CCO 1/16/9/9; 1.0 file
    - Bournemouth East, Feb 1972-Mar 1973; Jul-Nov 1977; CCO 1/16/9/10; 1.0 file
    - South Dorset, Mar 1973-Nov 1976; CCO 1/16/9/11; 1.0 file
    - Fareham, Jan 1972-Apr 1972; Mar-Oct 1975; CCO 1/16/9/12; 1.0 file
    - Southampton Itchen, Jun 1972-Oct 1975; CCO 1/16/9/13; 1.0 file
    - Gosport, Feb 1972-Nov 1973; CCO 1/16/9/14; 1.0 file
    - Wycombe, Mar 1973; Sep 1977-May 1978; CCO 1/16/9/15; 1.0 file
    - Poole, Dec 1972; Feb-Jul 1977; CCO 1/16/9/16; 1.0 file
    - Portsmouth North, Jul 1972-May 1976; CCO 1/16/9/17; 1.0 file
    - Aylesbury, Dec 1974-Apr 1975; CCO 1/16/9/18; 1.0 file
    - Buckingham, May 1973; CCO 1/16/9/19; 1.0 file
  - Area K - Western, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/10/1-CCO 1/16/10/16
    - Falmouth and Camborne, Feb 1972-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/10/1; 1.0 file
    - South-East Cornwall, Nov 1972-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/10/2; 1.0 file
      [Also known as Bodmin Constituency].
    - Weston Super Mare, Oct 1971-Sep 1975; CCO 1/16/10/3; 1.0 file
    - South Gloucestershire, Nov 1973-May 1974; Dec 1976; Jan 1983; CCO 1/16/10/4; 1.0 file
    - North Somerset, Mar 1972-Dec 1977; CCO 1/16/10/5; 1.0 file
    - Kingswood, Oct 1971-Nov 1981; CCO 1/16/10/6; 1.0 file
    - Bristol South, Feb 1973-Mar 1977; CCO 1/16/10/7; 1.0 file
    - Bristol West, Oct 1972-Mar 1976; CCO 1/16/10/8; 1.0 file
    - Bristol South East, Mar 1972-Feb 1978; CCO 1/16/10/9; 1.0 file
    - Bristol North West, Oct 1972-Feb 1980; CCO 1/16/10/10; 1.0 file
    - Bristol North East, Apr 1972-Feb 1976; CCO 1/16/10/11; 1.0 file
    - Bath, May 1972-Feb 1979; CCO 1/16/10/12; 1.0 file
    - Bristol, Jan 1981-Feb 1982; CCO 1/16/10/13; 1.0 file
    - St Ives, May 1974-Dec 1977; CCO 1/16/10/14; 1.0 file
    - North Devon, Feb 1971-Mar 1978; CCO 1/16/10/15; 1.0 file
    - North Cornwall, Jun 1970-May 1982; CCO 1/16/10/16; 1.0 file
  - Area L - Wales and Monmouthshire, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/11
  - Area M - Scotland, 1971-1982
    CCO 1/16/12/1-CCO 1/16/12/52
    - North Aberdeen, Dec 1982; CCO 1/16/12/1; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeen South, Sep 1982-Feb 1983; CCO 1/16/12/2; 1.0 file
    - East Aberdeenshire, Jan 1979; CCO 1/16/12/3; 1.0 file
    - South Angus, Mar 1981; CCO 1/16/12/4; 1.0 file
    - Argyll, Dec 1979-Feb 1983; CCO 1/16/12/5; 1.0 file
    - Central Ayrshire, Feb 1979-Feb 1982; CCO 1/16/12/6; 1.0 file
    - South Ayrshire, Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/12/7; 1.0 file
    - Bothwell, Jul 1979-Mar 1982; CCO 1/16/12/8; 1.0 file
    - Caithness & Sutherland, Dec 1979-Feb 1983; CCO 1/16/12/9; 1.0 file
    - Coatbridge & Airdrie, Mar 1981-Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/12/10; 1.0 file
    - Dumfries, Jul 1982; CCO 1/16/12/11; 1.0 file
    - East Dunbartonshire, Jan 1980; Mar 1981; CCO 1/16/12/12; 1.0 file
    - West Dunbartonshire, May 1981; Aug 1982; CCO 1/16/12/13; 1.0 file
    - Dundee East, Feb 1980-Apr 1982; CCO 1/16/12/14; 1.0 file
    - Dundee West, Sep 1979; CCO 1/16/12/15; 1.0 file
    - Central Edinburgh, Mar 1979-Mar 1981; CCO 1/16/12/16; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Feb 1980-Dec 1982; CCO 1/16/12/17; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Leith, Mar 1981-Dec 1982; CCO 1/16/12/18; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh North, May-Aug 1980; CCO 1/16/12/19; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh West, Feb-Oct 1980; CCO 1/16/12/20; 1.0 file
    - Central Fife, May 1980-Apr 1981; CCO 1/16/12/21; 1.0 file
    - East Fife, Nov 1978-Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/12/22; 1.0 file
    - City of Glasgow, Jan 1979; May 1981; CCO 1/16/12/23; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Cathcart, Jun 1982; Feb 1983; CCO 1/16/12/24; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Central, Mar 1980-Sep 1981; CCO 1/16/12/25; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Craigton, Feb 1980; CCO 1/16/12/26; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Garscadden, Nov 1978-Sep 1982; CCO 1/16/12/27; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Hillhead, Feb-Aug 1982; CCO 1/16/12/28; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Moaryhill, Mar 1979; Jun 1982; CCO 1/16/12/29; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Pollok, Dec 1978-Nov 1981; CCO 1/16/12/30; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Provan, Mar 1979; Apr 1982; CCO 1/16/12/31; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow Shettleston, Jun-Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/12/32; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow - Springburn, Nov 1978-Sep 1981; CCO 1/16/12/33; 1.0 file
    - Hamilton, May 1979; Oct 1982; CCO 1/16/12/34; 1.0 file
    - Inverness, Jan 1980; CCO 1/16/12/35; 1.0 file
    - Kelvingrove, Feb-Mar 1979; CCO 1/16/12/36; 1.0 file
    - East Kilbride, Mar 1981; Jan 1983; CCO 1/16/12/37; 1.0 file
    - Kilmarnock, Apr 1980; CCO 1/16/12/38; 1.0 file
    - Kirkcaldy, Feb 1980; CCO 1/16/12/39; 1.0 file
    - Lanark, Jun 1979; Mar 1981; CCO 1/16/12/40; 1.0 file
    - North Lanarkshire, Jul 1979; CCO 1/16/12/41; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Apr 1982; CCO 1/16/12/42; 1.0 file
    - Midlothian, Oct 1980; Jan 1982; CCO 1/16/12/43; 1.0 file
    - Motherwell & Wishaw, Aug 1982; CCO 1/16/12/44; 1.0 file
    - Orkney & Shetland, Dec 1978; Jul 1982; CCO 1/16/12/45; 1.0 file
    - Paisley, Aug 1982; Jan 1983; CCO 1/16/12/46; 1.0 file
    - East & West Renfrewshire, Jun 1982; Sep 1982; CCO 1/16/12/47; 1.0 file
    - Ross & Cromarty, Jun 1979-Jan 1981; CCO 1/16/12/48; 1.0 file
    - Rutherglen, Jul 1980; Jun 1981; CCO 1/16/12/49; 1.0 file
    - West Stirlingshire, Sep 1979-May 1980; CCO 1/16/12/50; 1.0 file
    - Western Isles, Jan 1979-Nov 1982; CCO 1/16/12/51; 1.0 file
    - Queen's Park, Mar 1979-Nov 1982; CCO 1/16/12/52; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, 1983-1989
  - Area A - Greater London, 1983-89
    CCO 1/17/1/1-CCO 1/17/1/3
    - Tottenham Constituency Association, 1983-87; CCO 1/17/1/1; 1.0 file
      Photocopies received with Research Department files.
    - Tottenham Constituency Association, 1988; CCO 1/17/1/2; 1.0 file
      Photocopies received with Research Department files
    - Tottenham Constituency Association, 1989; CCO 1/17/1/3; 1.0 file